Guide to the Vassar College Drama Department Records, circa 1910-2021
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
Vassar College Drama Department Records
circa 1910-2021
Vassar College. Department of Drama
72.5 cubic feet (106 boxes), 2 framed items
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
Material documenting the history of the Vassar College Drama Department and its many components and programs (including the Experimental Theatre). Includes programs, news clippings, production material, photographs, negatives, slides, and film.
Administrative History
The Vassar College Experimental Theatre was founded in 1925 by Hallie Flanagan Davis as a program of the English Department, and later became part of the Drama Department when it was founded in 1938. The predecessors of the Experimental Theatre included the Vassar Dramatic Workshop and the Vassar Players.
Scope and Content Note
Programs, news clippings, production material, photographs, slides, and negatives documenting the history of the Vassar College Drama Department and its many components and programs (including the Experimental Theatre) from about 1910-2021.
Access
Boxes 48, 96, 104, and 105 contain restricted material. Please contact the Archives and Special Collections staff for more information. The rest of the collection is open for research according to the regulations of the Vassar College Archives and Special Collections Library without any additional restrictions.
Related Materials
Hallie Flanagan Papers
Subject Headings
Names:
Flanagan, Hallie, 1890-1969
Organizations:
Experimental Theatre of Vassar College
Subjects:
College theater; Theater--Study and teaching; Performing arts--New York (State)--Poughkeepsie
Document Types:
Audiovisual materials; Clippings (information artifacts); Correspondence; Drawings (visual works); Negatives; Open reel audiotapes; Open reel videotapes; Photographs; Slides; Scripts; Sheet music
VCL Categories:
Vassar College Academic Departments and Programs
Encoding Information
Original encoding by Elizabeth Clarke, April 2007. Updated by Emma Gronbeck, October 2025.
Acquisition Information
Transferred in several accessions, 2008-2024. (A2008-019, A2009-048, A2013-025, A2014-030, A2018-017, A2018-018, A2020-003, A2024-027)
The records of Martin Fallon, technician and then an instructor in stage management for the Drama Department from approximately 1936-1944, were added to the collection in 2010, a gift of Charles D. Fallon (A2010-009).
The 2011 accession included photographs presumed to have been taken by Raymon Traver.
Series List
- Series I. Administrative Files, circa 1916-2021
  Programs, news clippings, promotional material, and other records relating to the Experimental Theatre and its productions as well as miscellaneous Drama Department files.
  Organized into two subseries: Subject Files; and Events, Publicity, and Drama Major Projects. Subject Files are arranged in box number order and Events, Publicity, and Drama Major Projects is arranged chronologically.
- Series II. Miscellaneous Student Papers and Theses, 1930-1973
  An incomplete set of student papers completed for various Drama Department classes.
  *Please note: Some Drama Department theses have been cataloged separately and can be accessed via the Vassar College Libraries Online Catalog.
- Series III. Experimental Theatre Visual Materials, 1925-1979
  This series contains photographic materials of productions of the Vassar Experimental Theatre, including lantern slides, negatives, and photographs.
  Organized into three subseries by format.
  - Lantern Slides, 1931, 1937
    Two sets of slides used in the Experimental Theatre productions, Can You Hear Their Voices (1931) and One-Third of a Nation (1937).
  - Negatives, 1925-1942
    Mostly 4"x5" negatives on cellulose acetate "Safety" film. Some are deteriorating and/or brittle and may not be available for duplication.
  - Photographs, 1925-1979
    Photographs housed according to size, then in chronological order.
    Boxes 10-21 and 68-79 contain 8" x 10" and smaller photographs
    Boxes 4-5 contain 14" x 18" and smaller photographs
    Boxes 22-24 contain 16" x 20" photographs
    Items housed in map cases are approximately 12" x 48"
    Only some of the photos in Box 25 are signed by Raymon Traver, but it is possible that all of them were taken by him.
    There are additional photographs in the production files housed in boxes 59 and 60 (A2013-025), as well as boxes 84-95.
- Series IV. Drama Department Slides, 1944-1991
  Four slide boxes within a larger box. Includes a set of numbered slides (with some numbers missing) of productions dating from 1944-1960. Also includes assorted undated slides from later accessions.
- Series V. Drama Department Audio and Film Reels, 1961-1971
  A small set of film and audio reels from miscellaneous productions.
- Series VI. Drama Department Production Material, circa 1910-2008
  Scripts, prompt books, costume and set designs, photographs, video recordings, and publicity materials for theatrical productions, including Experimental Theatre productions, Hall productions, senior theses*, and class projects. There is also a small collection of musical scores as well as the state management records of Martin Fallon, as well as other production scrapbooks, unsorted photographs, and miscellaneous materials. Boxes 59 and 60 include programs, correspondence, photographs and other materials relating to productions dating from 1915-1949.
  Organized into three subseries: Production Files, Stage Management Files, and Miscellaneous. Production Files and Stage Management Files are arranged chronologically. Miscellaneous files are arranged roughly in alphabetical order.
- Series VII. Drama Major Files, 1953-1999; [RESTRICTED]
  Files on Drama Department majors from each graduating class.
  Arranged chronologically.
Container List
- Series I. Administrative Files, 1916-2021
  - Subject Files, 1916-2006
    - Experimental Theatre News Clippings, 1929-1972 (Folder 1.1)
    - Experimental Theatre Press Releases, 1960-1992 (Folder 1.2)
    - Experimental Theatre Programs, 1928-1949 (Folder 1.3)
    - Experimental Theatre Programs, 1950-1979 (Folder 1.4)
    - Experimental Theatre Programs, 1980-2003 (Folder 1.5)
    - Experimental Theatre Calendars and other Advertising Material, 1934-2002, undated (Folder 1.6)
    - Experimental Theatre Report by Hallie Flanagan and Lester Lang, 1933 May 18 (Folder 1.7)
    - Experimental Theatre Building Plans, 1930 (Folder 1.8)
    - Experimental Theatre Production Files — Orpheus, 1939 (Folder 1.9)
    - Experimental Theatre Production Files — Pillars of Society, 1939 (Folder 1.10)
    - Predecessors to the Experimental Theatre at Vassar, circa 1917-1926 (Folder 1.11)
    - Mary Heinlein's Files, circa 1950-1955 (Folder 1.12)
    - Mary Heinlein's Files, circa 1956-1957 (Folder 1.13)
    - Mary Heinlein's Files, circa 1958-1959 (Folder 1.14)
    - Mary Heinlein's Files, circa 1959-1960 (Folder 1.15)
    - Mary Heinlein's Files, circa 1960-1961 (Folder 1.16)
    - Mary Heinlein's Files, circa 1960-1961 (Folder 1.17)
    - Mary Heinlein's Files, circa 1937-1960 (Folder 1.18)
    - Summer Session, 1935 (Folders 1.19-1.23)
    - Summer Session, 1935 (Folder 2.1)
    - Summer Session, 1935-1937 (Folder 2.2)
    - Correspondence with Lester Lang, 1937-1938 (Folder 2.3)
    - Correspondence with the Mercury Theatre, 1937-1938 (Folder 2.4)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1931-1937 (Folder 2.5)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1960-1961 (Folder 2.6)
    - Miscellaneous, circa 1928-1943 (Folder 2.7)
    - General Correspondence - B, 1946-1955 (Folder 46.1)
    - General Correspondence - C, 1947-1955 (Folder 46.2)
    - General Correspondence - H, 1948-1955 (Folder 46.3)
    - General Correspondence - L, 1949-1955 (Folder 46.4)
    - General Correspondence - M, 1946-1954 (Folder 46.5)
    - General Correspondence - P, 1946-1955 (Folder 46.6)
    - General Correspondence - S, 1940-1955 (Folders 46.7-46.8)
    - General Correspondence - W, 1940-1955 (Folder 46.9)
    - Courses Bibliographies, 1940-1953, undated (Folder 46.10)
    - Courses Bibliographies, 1941-1955, undated (Folder 46.11)
    - Courses Bibliographies, 1938-1944 (Folder 46.12)
    - Summer Theatre, 1954 (Folder 46.13)
    - Students Summer Drama Schools, undated (Folder 46.14)
    - Summer Theatre, 1956 (Folder 46.15)
    - Summer Theatre, 1955 (Folder 46.16)
    - College Library, 1951-1955 (Folder 46.17)
    - College Theatre — Avery, 1952 (Folder 46.18)
    - The Theatre — Avery, 1939-1953 (Folder 46.19)
    - Recorder — Old, undated (Folder 46.20)
    - Mailing list, 1951-1954 (Folder 46.21)
    - Curriculum Committee — Old, undated (Folder 46.22)
    - Publicity — Old, 1938-1953, undated (Folder 46.23)
    - National Theatre Conference, 1933-1949, undated (Folders 46.24 - 46.26)
    - National Theatre Conference, 1948-1949 (Folder 46.27)
    - National Theatre Conference, 1949-1953, undated (Folder 46.28)
    - National Theatre Conference Placement Service Catalogue, Section 1, 1948 (Folder 46.29)
    - New Dramatists Committee, undated (Folder 46.30)
    - N.Y. State Regional Drama: NY State Community Theatre Association, 1947-1953, undated (Folder 47.1)
    - Drama Department Scrapbook, circa 1916-1921 (Folder 47.1a)
    - Scrapbook of Theatre Clippings, 1936-1937 (Folder 47.2)
    - Scrapbook of Theatre Clippings, circa 1937 (Folder 47.3)
    - Scrapbook of Theatre Clippings, 1937-1938 (Folder 47.4)
    - Scrapbooks, containing programs, press clippings, correspondence, 1935-1945; (2 volumes) (Box 80 (Oversize))
    - Scrapbooks, containing programs, press clippings, photographs, correspondence, 1927-1936; (2 volumes) (Boxes 81-82 (Oversize))
    - Equipment — General, undated (Folder 47.5)
    - Costuming and Make-up, undated (Folder 47.6)
    - Sound Equipment and Effects, undated (Folder 47.7)
    - Lighting Equipment, undated (Folder 47.8)
    - Shuttuck, Charles H., 1948-1954, undated (Folder 47.9)
    - Faculty — Stewart, David, 1952; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 48.1)
    - "Faculty — (Coffee) Richards, Sally, ", 1949, 1951; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 48.2)
    - Applicants, 1946-1955; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 48.3)
    - Applicants for Miss Smith's Position, 1943-1948, undated; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 48.4)
    - Student letters, 1940-1954, undated; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 48.5)
    - Students' letters, 1950-1952; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 48.6)
    - Letters of Recommendation, 1941-1954; [RESTRICTED] (Folder 48.7)
    - Vassar Drama Alumnae, 1970-1999; (2 folders) (Box 94)
    - Vassar Drama Alumnae: Meryl Streep ('71), undated (Box 94)
    - Vassar Drama Alumnae, 1994 (Box 95)
    - Vassar College Alumnae Association, 1971-1994 (Box 95)
    - Experimental Theatre - Martin Fallon Records, 1933-1940 (Box 95)
    - [Newspaper Clippings], 2004-2006 (Box 95)
    - Photographs - Drama department yearbook photographs, 1998 (Box 95)
    - Powerhouse Theatre, 1972-1974 (Box 95)
    - Powerhouse Theater, 1973; (2 folders) (Box 95)
    - [Powerhouse Renovation] - Architect's for new theatre wing - Vassar Drama Dept, 1964-1966 (Box 95)
    - [Powerhouse Renovation] - Avery Theater Renovation, 1966-1976 (Box 95)
    - [Powerhouse Renovation] - College New Theatre, 1967-1971 (Box 95)
    - Powerhouse Renovation [1], 1968-1979 (Box 96)
    - Powerhouse Renovation [2], 1969-1971 (Box 96)
    - Powerhouse Renovation Budget [3], 1982-1985 (Box 96)
    - Powerhouse Renovation [4], 1967-1971 (Box 96)
    - Powerhouse Renovation [5], 1970 (Box 96)
    - Powerhouse Theatre, Hallie Flanagan Davis Dedication Plans, 1973-1988 (Box 96)
    - Powerhouse Theatre, Hallie Flanagan Davis Printed Info, 1973 (Box 96)
    - [Self-Study Report for Commission of Higher Ed.], 1979 Feb (Box 96)
    - Summer Theater, 1983-1985 (Box 96)
    - Summer Theater, 1987; (2 folders) (Box 96)
    - Syllabi - Drama 332, 1992-1994 (Box 96)
    - Theater Proposal, 1983 (Box 96)
    - Vassar Dance Theatre - Spring Concert, 1974? Apr 23-25 (Box 96)
    - Vassar 100th Anniversary, 1957-1961 (Box 96)
    - Drama Major's Committee Faculty Evaluations, circa 1992; [RESTRICTED] (Box 96)
    - Personnel, 1974-1994; [RESTRICTED] (Box 96)
  - Events, Publicity, and Drama Major Projects, 2003-2021
    - Marilyn Swartz Seven Playwriting, 2003 Apr (Box 93)
    - Tom Hanks Visit, 2003 Sep 17 - 19 (Box 93)
    - Anna Deavere Smith Visit, 2003 Oct 14 (Box 93)
    - Special Events, 2004 Spring (Box 93)
    - Special Events, 2004 Fall (Box 93)
    - Special Events, 2005 Spring (Box 93)
    - Special Events, 2007 Spring (Box 93)
    - Fall Publicity Posters, 2007 Fall (Box 93)
    - Special Event: Kim Brockington, 2008 Mar 1 (Box 93)
    - Special Event: Eunice Roberts, 2008 Apr (Box 93)
    - Publicity, 2008 Spring (Box 93)
    - Special Event: Bikel Brooks Concert, 2008 Feb 17 (Box 93)
    - Publicity, 2008 Fall (Box 93)
    - LAMDA Workshop, 2008 Nov (Box 93)
    - Frances Steerman Award Reception, 2008 Feb 26 (Box 93)
    - Junior Projects, 2009 Feb 14 - 16 (Box 93)
    - Marilyn Swartz Seven Playwriting, 2009 Apr (Box 93)
    - Sophomore Projects, 2009 Spring (Box 93)
    - Publicity, 2009 Spring (Box 93)
    - Publicity, 2009 Fall (Box 93)
    - Spring 2010 Shows and Publicity, 2010 Spring (Box 93)
    - Marilyn Swartz Seven Play Competition, 2009 - 2010 (Box 93)
    - Reading of Angels in America, 2010 Sep 16 - 19 (Box 93)
    - Publicity, 2010 Fall (Box 94)
    - Streep Studio Reading, 2010 Fall (Box 94)
    - Growing Wild Reading, 2011 Apr 20 (Box 94)
    - Streep Senior Readings, 2011 Spring (Box 94)
    - Spring Workshops, 2011 Spring (Box 94)
    - Spring Publicity, 2011 Spring (Box 94)
    - Fitz Patton '88 Sound Design, undated (Box 94)
    - A day at Vassar, 2011 Oct 15 (Box 94)
    - Workshops, 2011 - 2012 (Box 94)
    - Publicity, 2011 - 2012 (Box 94)
    - MSS Award, 2012 Apr 21 (Box 94)
    - BADA workshop, 2012 Sep 24 (Box 94)
    - Fall Semester, 2012 (Box 94)
    - Keb' Mo' Speaks, 2012 Oct 21 (Box 94)
    - Masking Workshop, 2012 Nov 2 - 3 (Box 94)
    - Drama Publicity, 2012 - 2013 (Box 94)
    - Sarah Ruhl visit, 2013 Apr 10 (Box 94)
    - American Soldier MSS, 2013 Apr (Box 94)
    - MSS Comp, 2013 Apr 21 (Box 94)
    - Pro Theater Workshop, 2013 Apr 22 (Box 94)
    - Publicity, 2013 - 2014 (Box 94)
    - Royalties, 2013 - 2014 (Box 94)
    - MSS Playwriting competition, 2013 - 2014 (Box 94)
    - St Nicholas Reading, 2014 Dec (Box 94)
    - Pretty Old, 2015 Feb 6 (Box 94)
    - Indigo MSS Playwriting Competition, 2015 Apr 19 (Box 94)
    - Fall Guest info Sessions, 2015 Fall (Box 94)
    - Larry Kramer, 2015 Oct 28 (Box 94)
    - Proposals, 2016 - 2017 (Box 94)
    - Nit Guest and BADA guest, 2016 Fall (Box 94)
    - Spring 2017 Events (Box 94)
    - Guests/Workshops, 2017 Fall (Box 94)
    - Readings, 2017 Fall (Box 94)
    - Proposals, 2017 - 2018 (Box 94)
    - Modfest, 2018 Feb 11 (Box 94)
    - Sophia Gutierrez, 2018 Spring (Box 94)
    - Uncovering Dress, 2018 Spring (Box 94)
    - Jennifer McCabe, 2018 Feb (Box 94)
    - Dallas Goldtooth, 2018 Feb (Box 94)
    - Harry Lennix Lecture, 2018 Apr 14 (Box 94)
    - John Leguizamo, 2018 Apr 19 (Box 94)
    - Briggs: Senior Project, 2018 Apr 26 - 28 (Box 94)
    - Wendall Harrington, 2018 Apr 27 (Box 94)
    - Proposals, 2018 - 2019 (Box 94)
    - Puppet Project, 2018 Nov 2 (Box 94)
    - Hilton, Bareket Sr Proposal, 2019 (Box 94)
    - Nadine Mozon, 2019 Mar 1 (Box 94)
    - Mandy Barrington, 2019 Sep 13 (Box 94)
    - CAAD-EPI, 2019 (Box 94)
    - Annual Visits: NTI, BADA, LAMDA, 2019 Fall (Box 94)
    - MSS Play Award, 2020 Apr 26 (Box 94)
    - MSS Playwriting Award, 2018 Apr 29 (Box 94)
    - MSS Playwriting award Reception, 2019 Apr 28 (Box 94)
    - Peter Buffet, 2020 Mar 3 (Box 94)
    - Story Collide, 2020 Apr 28 (Box 94)
    - Annual Playwriting Award, 2021 May 22 (Box 94)
    - New Play Festival, 2021 May 21 - 22 (Box 94)
    - Louis Blanchman, 2021 Dec (Box 94)
- Series II. Miscellaneous Student Papers and Theses, 1930-1973
  - Miscellaneous Student Papers and Theses, 1930-1973 (Box 2)
- Series III. Experimental Theatre Visual Materials, 1925-1979
  - Lantern Slides, 1931, 1937
    - Can You Hear Their Voices?, 1931 May (Box 3)
    - One-Third of a Nation, 1937 Jul (Box 3)
  - Negatives, 1925-1940s
    - Guibour, 1925-1926 (Folder 6.1)
    - Marriage Proposal, 1927 Nov (Folder 6.2)
    - Sleeping Beauty, 1928 Apr (Folder 6.3)
    - Blocks, 1928 Apr (Folder 6.4)
    - Troll Hill, 1928 Oct (Folder 6.5)
    - Down in Egypt's Land, 1928 Dec (Folder 6.6)
    - Water and Wine, 1928 Dec (Folder 6.7)
    - Noah's Ark, circa 1928 (Folder 6.8)
    - The Wreck, 1929 Mar (Folder 6.9)
    - The Sky Will be Lit Up, 1929 Apr (Folder 6.10)
    - X=O, 1929 Oct (Folder 6.11)
    - Each in His Own Way, 1929 Dec (Folder 6.12)
    - Simples by Moonlight / Cartoon, 1930 Mar (Folder 6.13)
    - Man and the Masses, 1930 May (Folder 6.14)
    - Backgrounds of Modern Theatre?, [1930 Oct] (Folder 6.15)
    - The Adoption, 1930 Dec (Folder 6.16)
    - The Other Room, 1930 Dec (Folder 6.17)
    - Groceries and Notions, 1931 Feb (Folder 6.18)
    - Can You Hear Their Voices?, 1931 May (Folder 6.19)
    - See America First, 1931 Oct (Folder 6.20)
    - The Man with the Flower in his Mouth, 1931 Oct (Folder 6.21)
    - Hippolytus, 1931 Dec (Folder 6.22)
    - See America Now, 1932 Oct (Folder 6.23)
    - Varieta Futurista, 1932 Mar (Folder 7.1)
    - Miners on Strike, 1932 May (Folder 7.2)
    - We Demand, 1932 May (Folder 7.3)
    - Heritage, 1932 May (Folder 7.4)
    - Svapnavasavadatta of Bhasa (Dream of the Vasavadatta), 1933 Jan (Folder 7.5)
    - Now I Know Love, 1933 (Folders 7.6-7.7)
    - American Plan, 1933 Oct (Folder 7.8)
    - Fear, 1934 Jan (Folder 7.9)
    - The Phantom Bride!, 1934 May (Folder 7.10)
    - Singing Girl of Copan, 1934 Mar (Folder 7.11)
    - Antony and Cleopatra, 1934 Dec (Folders 7.12-7.13)
    - My Country Right or Left, 1935 May (Folder 8.1)
    - Ladies are Made, 1935 Jul (Folder 8.2)
    - The Phantom Bride!, 1935 Jul (Folder 8.3)
    - Come Out Into the Sun, 1935 Aug (Folder 8.4)
    - Lady from the Sea, 1935 Dec (Folder 8.5)
    - Lab Shows, 1936 Feb (Folder 8.6)
    - Fuente Ovejuna, 1936 May (Folder 8.7)
    - Tonight We Improvise, 1936 Dec (Folder 8.8)
    - Lab Shows, 1937 Jan (Folder 8.9)
    - No More Peace (blue-ing), 1937 Feb (Folder 8.10)
    - No More Peace, 1937 Feb (Folder 8.11)
    - Relax!, 1937 Apr (Folder 8.12)
    - Fallen Mangoes, 1937 Apr (Folder 8.13)
    - One-Third of a Nation, 1937 Jul (Folder 8.14)
    - The Infernal Machine, 1937 Dec (Folder 8.15)
    - Knight of the Burning Pestle, 1938 Feb (Folder 8.16)
    - 3 Plays on American Homelife, 1938 Apr (Folder 9.1)
    - Vassar's Folly, 1938 Dec (Folder 9.2)
    - Peter Goes to the Fair, 1939 Feb (Folder 9.3)
    - Three Sisters, 1939 Apr (Folder 9.4)
    - Orpheus, 1939 Dec (Folder 9.5)
    - Mr. Sycamore, 1940 Feb (Folder 9.6)
    - Vassar's Folly, 1940 (Folder 9.7)
    - Our Town, 1940 Dec (Folder 9.8)
    - Pillars of Society, 1941 Feb (Folder 9.9)
    - Sight Unseen, 1941 Apr (Folder 9.13)
    - Murder in the Cathedral, 1941 Dec (Folder 9.14)
    - Santos Vega, 1942 Feb (Folder 9.10)
    - Phoenix, 1942 Apr (Folder 9.11)
    - War Chest Rally, 1942 Nov (Folder 9.12)
    - Unidentified Production, circa 1940s (Folder 9.15)
    - War Bonds Posters - for set design?, circa 1930s (Folder 9.16)
    - Costume Designs?, circa 1930s (Folder 9.17)
    - Rosenfeld Costume Designs?, circa 1930s (Folder 9.18)
  - Photographs, 1925-1979
    - Guibour, 1925-1926 (Folder 10.1)
    - Guibour, 1925-1926 (Folder 68.1)
    - Guibour, 1925-1926 (Map Case - F1)
    - She Canna Perish, 1926 Mar (Folder 68.2)
    - The King’s Ward, 1926 Mar (Folder 68.2)
    - Marriage Proposal, 1927 Nov (Folder 10.2)
    - Ur Faust, 1927 (Folder 10.3)
    - The Marriage Proposal, 1928 Mar (Folder 68.4)
    - Blocks, 1928 Apr (Folder 10.4)
    - Blocks, 1928 Apr (Folder 68.6)
    - Blocks, 1928 Apr (Map Case - F1)
    - Sleeping Beauty, 1928 Apr (Folder 10.5)
    - The Sleeping Beauty, 1928 Apr (Folder 68.5)
    - Troll Hill, 1928 Oct (Folder 10.6)
    - Troll Hill, 1928 Oct (Folder 68.7)
    - Troll Hill, 1928 Oct (Map Case - F1)
    - Water and Wine, 1928 Dec (Folder 10.7)
    - Down in Egypt's Land, 1928 Dec (Folder 10.8)
    - Down in Egypt's Land, 1928-1929 (Folder 68.8)
    - Lorenzo the Magnificent, 1928 (Folder 68.3)
    - The Sky Will be Lit Up, 1929 Apr (Folder 10.9)
    - The Sky Will be Lit Up, 1929 Apr (Folder 68.12)
    - The Sky Will be Lit Up, set illustration, unknown artist, [1929 Apr?]; (framed) (On shelf)
    - Water and Wine, 1928-1929 (Folder 68.9)
    - The Prophecy, 1928-1929 (Folder 68.10)
    - The Prophecy, 1928-1929 (Map Case - F1)
    - The Wreck, 1928-1929 (Folder 68.11)
    - X=O, 1929 Oct (Folder 10.10)
    - Endurance Flight, 1929 Oct (Folder 68.13)
    - Each In His Own Way, 1929 Dec (Folder 68.14)
    - Each In His Own Way, 1929 Dec (Folder 10.11)
    - Cartoon, 1929-1930 (Folder 68.15)
    - Cartoon, 1929-1930 (Map Case - F1)
    - Simples By Moonlight, 1930 Mar (Folder 68.18)
    - Man and the Masses, 1930 May (Folder 10.12)
    - Man and the Masses, 1930 May (Folder 68.17)
    - Background of Modern Theatre, 1930 Oct (Folders 10.13-10.14)
    - Background of Modern Theatre, 1930 Oct (Map Case - F2)
    - The Adoption, 1930 Dec (Folder 11.1)
    - The Adoption, 1930 Dec (Folder 68.19)
    - The Adoption, 1930 Dec (Map Case - F2)
    - The Other Room, 1930 Dec (Folder 11.2)
    - The Ivory Door, 1930 (Folder 68.16)
    - The Strange Gentleman, 1930-1931 (Folder 69.1)
    - Groceries and Notions, 1931 Feb (Folders 11.3-11.4)
    - Groceries and Notions, 1930-1931 (Folder 69.2)
    - Groceries and Notions, 1931 Feb (Map Case - F2)
    - Can You Hear Their Voices?, 1931 May (Folders 11.5-11.6)
    - Can You Hear Their Voices?, 1931 May (Folder 69.4)
    - See America First, 1931 Oct (Folder 11.7)
    - See America First, 1931 Oct (Map Case - F2)
    - The Man with the Flower in his Mouth, 1931 Oct (Folder 11.8)
    - The Man with the Flower in his Mouth, 1931 Oct (Map Case - F2)
    - Hippolytus, 1931 Dec (Folders 11.9-11.10)
    - Hippolytus, 1931 Dec (Folder 22.1 (Oversize))
    - The Hippolytus of Euripides, 1931 (Folder 69.3)
    - Varieta Futurista, 1932 Mar (Folder 11.11)
    - Varieta Futurista, 1932 (Folder 69.5)
    - Heritage, 1932 May (Folder 12.1)
    - Heritage, 1932 May (Folder 69.6)
    - Heritage, 1932 May (Map Case - F2)
    - We Demand, 1932 May (Folder 69.6)
    - We Demand, 1932 May (Map Case - F2)
    - Miners on Strike, 1932 May (Folder 69.6)
    - See America Now, 1932 Oct (Folder 12.2)
    - See America Now, 1932 Oct (Map Case - F3)
    - Svapnavasavadatta of Bhasa (Dream of the Vasavadatta), 1933 Jan (Folders 12.4-12.5)
    - Svapnavasavadatta of Bhasa (Dream of the Vasavadatta), 1933 Jan (Folder 22.2 (Oversize))
    - American Plan, 1933 Oct (Folder 69.7)
    - Now I Know Love, 1933 (Folder 12.6)
    - Fear, 1934 Jan (Folder 12.7)
    - Fear, 1934 Jan (Map Case - F3)
    - Backgrounds of the Modern Theatre, 1934 Mar (Folder 12.8)
    - Backgrounds of the Modern Theatre, 1934 Mar (Folder 69.8)
    - Backgrounds of the Modern Theatre, 1934 Mar (Map Case - F3)
    - Trial By Jury, 1934 Apr (Folder 69.9)
    - The Phantom Bride!, 1934 May (Folder 12.9)
    - The Phantom Bride!, 1934 May (Folder 13.1)
    - The Phantom Bride!, 1934 May (Folder 69.10)
    - The Phantom Bride!, 1934 May (Map Case - F3)
    - Noah, 1934 Jun (Folder 69.11)
    - Antony and Cleopatra, 1934 Dec (Folders 13.2-13.3)
    - Antony and Cleopatra, 1934 Dec (Folder 69.12)
    - Antony and Cleopatra, 1934 Dec (Map Case - F4)
    - The First Legion, 1934 (Folder 22.3 (Oversize))
    - My Country Right or Left, 1935 May (Map Case - F4)
    - Ladies are Made, 1935 Jul (Folders 13.4-13.5)